// Array of questions with options and correct answers
const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "______ is a country (enclaved) within a country? ",
    answer: "Lesotho",
    options: [
      "Palestine",
      "Palau",
      "Lesotho",
      "Bosnia and Herzegovina"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "_______ has won the 2020 Tyler Prize for Environmental Achievement ?",
    answer: "Pavan Sukhdev",
    options: [
      "Pavan Sukhdev",
      "Sunil Arora",
      "Anil Khanna",
      "Sanjana Kapoor"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "__________ was the first ruler of soomra dynasty (1011-1026)? ",
    answer: "Al-khafif",
    options: [
      "Hameer",
      "Dodo",
      "Chanesar",
      "Al-khafif"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "‘History of Wolves’ book was written by: ",
    answer: "Emily Fridlund",
    options: [
      "Angie Thomas ",
      "Aysha jalal ",
      "Emily Fridlund",
      "Margaret Wilkerson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "“Asiana” Airline is belongs to _________ ? ",
    answer: "South Korea ",
    options: [
      "Afghanistan",
      "South Korea ",
      "Syria",
      "Iraq"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "“Decision Point” Book is written by____________.",
    answer: "George W Bush ",
    options: [
      "Barack Obama",
      "Bill Clinton ",
      "Richard Nixon",
      "George W Bush "
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "“Guns, Germs, and Steel book” is written by ________ ?",
    answer: "Jared Mason Diamond",
    options: [
      "Jared Mason Diamond",
      "Barbara Tuchman",
      "James McPherson",
      "William Manchester"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "“Izmir Adnan Menderes Airport” is located in_________?",
    answer: "Turkey",
    options: [
      "Egypt",
      "UAE",
      "Turkey",
      "Cyprus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "“JANA” is the news agency of_________? ",
    answer: "Libya",
    options: [
      "Japan",
      "Russia",
      "China",
      "Libya"
    ]
    },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "“Kouprey” is the national animal of__________? ",
    answer: "Cambodia",
    options: [
      "Nigeria",
      "Cambodia",
      "Mongolia",
      "N.O.T"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "“Night watch” is a famous_____________? ",
    answer: "Painting",
    options: [
      "Painting",
      "Restaurant",
      "Hotel",
      "Beach"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "“Operation Pluto” was planned by__________? ",
    answer: "U.S",
    options: [
      "U.S",
      "Italy",
      "Russia",
      "Sri Lanka "
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "“Port of Barrow” is the seaport of ___________ ? ",
    answer: "UK",
    options: [
      "USA",
      "UK",
      "Australia",
      "Canada"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "“Ratoons” is associated with__________? ",
    answer: "Sugarcane",
    options: [
      "Sugarcane",
      "Wheat",
      "Rice",
      "Desert"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "“San Julian” is the seaport of _______ ? ",
    answer: "Argentina",
    options: [
      "Australia",
      "Argentina",
      "Aruba",
      "Azerbaijan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "“Shah-jo-Risalo” a famous book of Shah Abdul Latif was first published in which city? ",
    answer: "Leipzig",
    options: [
      "Leipzig",
      "Geneva",
      "London",
      "Rome"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "“Shewala Teja singh temple” reopened after 72 years. it is located in _______ city of Pakistan. ",
    answer: "Sialkot",
    options: [
      "Multan",
      "Faislabad",
      "Sialkot",
      "Sheikhupura"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "“Siachen Glacier” is situated in_______? ",
    answer: "Karakorum",
    options: [
      "Sulaiman",
      "Hindu Kush ",
      "Pamir",
      "Karakorum"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "“There is no God other than God and Muhammad (ﷺ) is his Prophet” Is The National Motto of_________?",
    answer: "Saudi Arabia ",
    options: [
      "Saudi Arabia ",
      "Iraq",
      "Syria",
      "Egypt"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "“Zeebrugge ” is the seaport of ________ ? ",
    answer: "Belgium",
    options: [
      "Bahrain",
      "Bangladesh",
      "Belgium",
      "N.O.T"
    ]
  },
];